[
  {
    "question": "Radhika got 16th rank from the top and 13th rank from the bottom in an exam. How many students are there in the class?",
    "option_1": "30",
    "option_2": "27",
    "option_3": "29",
    "option_4": "28",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "In a row of people, Ram is 18th from the left and 23rd from the right. How many people are there in the row?",
    "option_1": "40",
    "option_2": "41",
    "option_3": "42",
    "option_4": "39",
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "In a row of trees, the lemon tree is 13th from either end. How many trees are there in the row?",
    "option_1": "26",
    "option_2": "25",
    "option_3": "24",
    "option_4": "27",
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the row of people, A is 13th from the left and 19th from the right. How many people are there in that row?",
    "option_1": "32",
    "option_2": "31",
    "option_3": "30",
    "option_4": "33",
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "There are 47 cars in a row. The black car is 18th from the right end and the white car is 39th from the right end. How many cars are there between the black and white cars?",
    "option_1": "21",
    "option_2": "20",
    "option_3": "19",
    "option_4": "18",
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "If 27th May 2007 is Sunday, then what day of the week will be 25th May 2018?",
    "option_1": "Thursday",
    "option_2": "Sunday",
    "option_3": "Friday",
    "option_4": "Saturday",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which day of the week was it in January 2009?",
    "option_1": "Sunday",
    "option_2": "Friday",
    "option_3": "Saturday",
    "option_4": "Monday",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "If exactly 1 year and 2 days later it is Tuesday, then what day is today? This is not a leap year.",
    "option_1": "Monday",
    "option_2": "Tuesday",
    "option_3": "Sunday",
    "option_4": "Saturday",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "If 7th May 2000 is Sunday, then what day of the week will be on 15th July 2010?",
    "option_1": "Monday",
    "option_2": "Sunday",
    "option_3": "Friday",
    "option_4": "Thursday",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "If 29 January 2003 is Wednesday, then what day of the week will be on 26 February 2005?",
    "option_1": "Saturday",
    "option_2": "Sunday",
    "option_3": "Friday",
    "option_4": "Thursday",
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "The angle formed by the hour and minute hands at 3:25 in a clock is:",
    "option_1": "32°",
    "option_2": "65°",
    "option_3": "54°",
    "option_4": "47.5°",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "At what time between 4 o'clock and 5 o'clock will the two hands of a clock make a right angle to each other for the first time?",
    "option_1": "4 o'clock 60 / 11 minutes",
    "option_2": "4 o'clock 420 / 11 minutes",
    "option_3": "4 o'clock 58 / 11 minutes",
    "option_4": "4 o'clock 422 / 11 minutes",
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the smaller of the two angles made by the hour hand and the minute hand at 9:22 pm?",
    "option_1": "149°",
    "option_2": "150°",
    "option_3": "138°",
    "option_4": "150.5°",
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "If the hour hand of a clock moves forward by 18°, then by how many degrees will the minute hand move during the same time?",
    "option_1": "168",
    "option_2": "196",
    "option_3": "216",
    "option_4": "276",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ramya looks at her wall clock and the clock shows 3:50, where the hour hand is pointing towards east. Which way is the minute hand pointing towards?",
    "option_1": "South East",
    "option_2": "North West",
    "option_3": "North East",
    "option_4": "South West",
    "answer": "2"
  }
]
